<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Itenerary on The Batson Wedding</title><link>http://example.org/pages/</link><description>Recent content in Itenerary on The Batson Wedding</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 19:41:12 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Itenerary</title><link>http://example.org/pages/itenerary/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 19:41:12 -0400</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/pages/itenerary/</guid><description>Please note there is a free parking spaces located at the hotel booked for the Batson wedding. There is free parking located at the ceremony church, however, the museum has paid parking (not covered by the Bride and Groom). It is encouraged to utilize the provided transportation between venues and parking at the hotel. 12:45 PM First Bus leaves Hotel to arrive to church
Marriott Courtyard Ottawa East 200 Coventry Road Ottawa ON, K1K 4S3 1:30 PM Final Bus leaves Hotel to arrive to church</description></item><item><title>Accomodations</title><link>http://example.org/pages/accomodations/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 19:40:06 -0400</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/pages/accomodations/</guid><description> We look forward to seeing you in Ottawa! For your convinience we have arranged a group rate at the Marriott Marriott Courtyard Ottawa East 200 Coventry Road Ottawa ON, K1K 4S3 Book Here</description></item><item><title>FAQ</title><link>http://example.org/pages/faq/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 18:16:11 -0400</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/pages/faq/</guid><description>If you have any additional questions, please email us at thebatsonswedding@gmail.com Where is the ceremony? Britannia United Church 985 Pinecrest Road Ottawa, ON K2B 6B4 Where is the ceremony? Britannia United Church 985 Pinecrest Road Ottawa, ON K2B 6B4 Where is the reception? Canada Aviation and Space Museum 11 Aviation Parkway Ottawa, ON K1K 2X5 Where is the reception? Canada Aviation and Space Museum 11 Aviation Parkway Ottawa, ON K1K 2X5 What time should I arrive?</description></item><item><title>Our Story</title><link>http://example.org/pages/our-story/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 18:15:49 -0400</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/pages/our-story/</guid><description>According to Lauren Lauren and Adam met on August 16, 2015, while moving into the Lennox and Addington residence building, they both worked for the university as residence fellows (Adam on the 10th floor and Lauren on the 3rd floor). Actually, it’s a bit of a funny story, Lauren actually met Adam’s Dad, Steve first. Steve would commonly tell Lauren to use the elevators to move her stuff to her room and Lauren said she was fine walking her stuff up the 3 flights of stairs.</description></item></channel></rss>